http://www.soundstrue.com/pages/privacy-policy

Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
Regular price
Starting at:
see all customer favorites
Erica Ariel Fox: What if the Problem is You? How to Win from WithinTuesday, July 21, 2020
Sarah Blondin: Kneeling at the Doorway of Your HeartTuesday, June 2, 2020
most recent podcast
Matthieu Ricard: Finding Inner FreedomTuesday, December 8th, 2020
Regular price
Starting at:
PRIVACY POLICY
Sounds True, Inc. (“Company,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through this Privacy Policy. It is our continued honor to serve you as a customer. We fully recognize our responsibility to protect your customer information and its confidential nature, and we employ the highest standards of safety, security, and confidentiality with your personal and financial information.
This Privacy Policy governs your access to and use of SoundsTrue.com and its affiliated sites, including any content, functionality, and services offered on or through SoundsTrue.com (“the Website”) whether as a guest or a registered user.
When accessing the Website, the Company will learn certain information about you both automatically and through voluntary actions you may take during your visit. This policy applies to information we collect on the Website and in email, text, or other electronic messages between you and the Website.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before you start to use the Website. By using the Website, making a purchase, or clicking to accept or agree to the Terms of Use when this option is made available to you, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by the Privacy Policy. If you do not want to agree to the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Website.
“Cookies” are small bits of information that your Web browser stores on your computer's hard drive. In order to purchase products from the Website, your Web browser must be enabled to accept cookies. We also use cookies to give credit to those sites that direct traffic to the Website for marketing purposes. The Company does not use cookies to store or collect personal information such as full names, addresses, or payment information.
CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13
Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or through any of its features, register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use.
If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@soundstrue.com.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU
When you access the Website, the Company will learn certain information about you during your visit
Information You Provide to Us: The Website provides various places for users to provide information. We collect information that users provide by filling out forms on the Website, communicating with us via contact forms, responding to surveys, search queries on our search feature, providing comments or other feedback, and providing information when ordering a product or service via the Website.
We use information you provide to us to deliver the requested product and/or service, to improve our overall performance, and to provide you with offers, promotions, and information.
Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technology: As you navigate through our Website, we use automatic data collection technologies including Google Analytics to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. This will generally include information about your location, your traffic pattern through our Website, and any communications between your computer and our Website. Among other things, we will collect data about the type of computer you use, your Internet connection, your IP address, your operating system, and your browser type.
The information we collect automatically is used for statistical data and will not include personal information. We use this data to improve our Website and our service offerings. To the extent that you voluntarily provide personal information to us, our systems will associate the automatically collected information with your personal information.
USE OF COOKIES AND PIXELS
Similar to other commercial websites, our Website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and server logs to collect information about how our Website is used. Information gathered through cookies and server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Website, and the websites visited just before and just after our own, as well as your IP address.
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
In order to purchase products from the Website, your web browser must be enabled to accept cookies. Among other things, we use cookies to give credit to those sites that direct traffic to the Website for marketing purposes. The Company does not use cookies to store or collect personal information such as full names, addresses, or payment information.
The Company also uses the technological equivalents of cookies, including social media pixels. These pixels allow social media sites to track visitors to outside websites so as to tailor advertising messages users see while visiting that social media website. The Company reserves the right to use these pixels in compliance with the policies of the various social media sites.
THIRD PARTY USE OF COOKIES
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.
We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly and review the privacy policies of each website you visit.
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, through mail, and via telephone. This also applies when you register for our Website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address, or make a purchase on this Website. For further information, see the email policies below.
We are committed to keeping your email address confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists to third parties, and will not disclose your email address to any third parties except as allowed in the section titled DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION.
We will maintain the information you send via email in accordance with applicable federal law.
In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all emails sent from our organization will clearly state who the email is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all email messages will also contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further email communication from us.
HOW AND WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION
The Company collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you register to download a book or resources, sign up for our newsletter, and/or purchase a product from us, we collect your information. We use this information to track your preferences and to keep you informed about the products and services you have selected to receive and any related products and/or services. As a visitor to this Website, you can engage in most activities without providing any personal information. It is only when you seek to download resources and/or register for services that you are required to provide information.
If you are outside the European Union and opt to receive free resources, participate in any free training programs, register for a webinar, register for a live event, register for a seminar, or purchase any products sold by the Company on this Website, we will enroll you to receive email and postal communications in the future, including updates that we believe you may find of interest.
If you are in the European Union and opt to receive any free resources, participate in any free training programs, register for a webinar, register for a live event, register for a seminar, or purchase any products sold by the Company on this Website, we will only enroll you to receive email and postal communications in the future, including updates that we believe you may find of interest, if you affirmatively consent to it.
If you are subscribed to receive updates, you may unsubscribe at any time. We include an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email we send. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email message, calling, or sending a written message, as follows:
Phone: Please call toll-free 1-800-333-9185 to speak to a Customer Service associate between 8 AM and 5 PM, Mountain time.
Email: Send us an email: support@soundstrue.com
Written Message: Sounds True, Attn: Customer Service, 413 S. Arthur Avenue, Louisville, CO 80027 USA
HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?
We use personal information for purposes of presenting our Website and its contents to you, providing you with information, providing you with offers for products and services, providing you with information about your subscriptions and products, carrying out any contract between you and the Company, administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.
From time to time, we may use the information you provide to us to make you offers to purchase products and services provided by third parties in exchange for a commission to be paid to us by such third parties. Should you opt to take part in such promotions, the third parties will receive your information.
From time to time, we may use the information you provide to us to display advertisements to you that are tailored to your personal characteristics, interests, and activities.
We may use software programs to create summary statistics from the information we collect, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our Website, assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
As a general rule, we do not sell, rent, lease, or otherwise transfer any information collected whether automatically or through your voluntary action.
We may disclose your personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliates, and service providers for the purpose of providing our services to you.
If you opt in for marketing associated with certain online courses, we do share your contact information with the course authors.
If you opt in to take part in third-party promotions offered on our Website, we will share your information with such third parties.
We may disclose your personal information to a third party, including a lawyer or collection agency, when necessary to enforce our terms of service or any other agreement between you and the Company. Additionally, we also provide your information to: Bronto, Klaviyo, Facebook, Google, Microsoft, Hotjar, Steelhouse, HasOffers, Nextopia, Kount, and other third-party service providers that we utilize.
We may provide your information to any successor in interest in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets and/or business.
In other words, we may disclose information when legally compelled to do so when we in good faith believe that the law requires it, for the protection of our legal rights, or when compelled by a court or other governmental entity to do so.
HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION AND SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS?
We employ commercially reasonable methods to ensure the security of the information you provide to us and the information we collect automatically. This includes using standard security protocols and working only with reputable third-party vendors. No data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and thus we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.
Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our Website may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit card and other sensitive information should never be transmitted via email.
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, the Company uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
CCPA
Except as set forth above in DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION, we do not sell, rent, lease, or otherwise transfer any personal information collected whether automatically or through your voluntary action.
California residents have the right to:
• know what data we have collected about them and receive a copy of that data.
• know if their data is being sold or disclosed for a business purpose to others.
• request that the data not be sold.
• request that their data be deleted unless it is necessary for any of the exceptions listed in the CCPA. If you request deletion of your data, we inform you if or how this will affect your use of the Website, subscription services, or ordering of products or services.
• not be discriminated against for exercising their CCPA rights.
We require only the information that is reasonably required for the specific purpose of providing the goods or services you request from us.
Please contact us at support@soundstrue.com or call us toll-free at 1-800-333-9185 should you have any questions, wish to request any information or action by us, or to exercise the rights above. We will respond to your requests free of charge.
POLICY CHANGES
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website homepage. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the bottom of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date, active, and deliverable email address for you, as well as for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.
Contact Us:
The Company welcomes your questions or comments regarding the Privacy Policy:
Sounds True, Inc.
413 S. Arthur Avenue
Louisville, CO 80027
Email address: support@soundstrue.com
GDPR Rights
If you are within the European Union, you are entitled to certain information and have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation.
Those rights include:
• We will retain any information you choose to provide to us until whichever of the following comes first: a) you ask us to delete the information; (b) our decision to cease using our existing data providers; or (c) the Company decides that the value in retaining the data is outweighed by the costs of retaining it.
• You have the right to request access to your personal data that the Company stores and the rights to either correct or erase your personal data or to cease any further dissemination of your personal data. You have the right to have us request that any third party that has received your personal data for an authorized purpose also cease to use and further disseminate your personal data.
• Please note that the Company may need to retain some information about you to satisfy our legal and security obligations. For instance, your information may remain in our back-up storage or archive even if you ask us to delete it.
• You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your personal data and to be notified of any breach of your personal data within 72 hours of the Company becoming aware of the breach.
• You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data and the right to the portability (export) of a copy of your personal data to you free of charge.
• To the extent that you provided consent to the Company’s processing of your personal data, or your consent to be provided with promotional or marketing materials or information, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based upon consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal of consent.
• You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that has jurisdiction over issues related to the General Data Protection Regulation.
We require only the information that is reasonably required to enter into a contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us.
Our GDPR Representative
The Company employs VeraSafe as its representative for handling General Data Protection Regulation issues.
22 Essex Way #8203
Essex, VT 05451
USA
Phone: 1-888-376-1079
Privacy Policy was last revised on March 23, 2020.
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection
x
x
